Mom, Dad
You've worked hard
Go get some sleep
I'm exhausted
That Lewes
treats us like workhorses
Thousands of pounds of feed
My old back and arms
are about to break
By the way, Mom, Dad
hurry back and sleep
Early tomorrow morning
we have to clean the frog waste
Still more to do
Honey
message Daniel quickly
If we keep this up
it'll be the death of me
Did you get the formula
No
Lewes is guarding it closely
He won't let me or
your mother near the mixing room
That heartless Lewes
is working us to death
Your father and I
at our age
He made us mix
thousands of pounds of feed
My back is killing me
If we don't get the formula
my arms will break
Mr. Zeth
only gave us three days
Only two days left now
Lewes won't let us in the mixing room
And he just finished mixing today
Won't need more for at least three days
We're out of time
Find a way
to ruin the feed he mixed
Force him to mix more
Then hide a camera
secretly in the mixing room
As for the rest
leave it to me
So you really are after the formula
Since you want it so badly
I'll give you one